A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4 FA457
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4
1966, 1969-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller).
FA457
13.2 Cubic Feet 11 record storage cartons.
Other Finding Aids
For other Nelson A. Rockefeller photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA454 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Nelson A. Rockefeller family, Series 1008
FA455 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2
FA456 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3
FA458 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands, Series 5
FA459 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6
FA460 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Unprocessed photographs, Series 7
File Plan note
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records are formerly classified as III 15.
Notations to RG 15 are used in this collection guide. If/when the notations in this guide are revised, an updated version of the guide will be made available for scholarly access.
Arrangement note
The Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs are arranged in the following series:
Series 1008: Nelson A. Rockefeller family. Series 2: Room 5600, Rockefeller family office. Series 3: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 4: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 5: Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands. Series 6: Vice Presidential. Series 7: Unprocessed photographs.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
Rockefeller family photographic holdings are arranged into the following series:
Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001. William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002. John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003. William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004. John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005. Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006. John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007. Nelson A. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1008. Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009. David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010.
Other Finding Aids note
For other Rockefeller family photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA445 Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001
FA446 William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002
FA447 John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003
FA448 William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004
FA449 John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005
FA450 Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006
FA451 John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007
FA452 Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009
FA453 David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: photographs.
Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Political campaigns -- United States; Rockefeller family -- Art collections; State governments -- United States; Art, Modern; Arts
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 1966, 1969-1973; 4; 13.2 Cubic Feet 11 record storage cartons.
  - Robert A. (Bob) Wands Photos
    - Contact Prints
      - 1970
        Scope and Contents
        The following is a guide, by month, of events photographed during the 1970 Rockefeller Gubernatorial Campaign. Events were photographed consecutively beginning April 21 and running through election night on November 3rd.
        One important set of photographs, The Rochester Republican State Nominating Convention of April 6, was produced by Wide World Photos. Proof sheets are in our archives.
        During the week of August 10 through 15, the Governor attended an outstanding variety of events. That week was selected as "A Week in the Life of the Governor During Campaign". Many important & exciting photographs are contained in these proofs & one complete set is located separately.
        Unless otherwise specified, all photography has been performed by Bob Wands, Official Campaign Photographer for Governor Rockefeller.
        Special assignments by B&G International and by Wide World Photos are listed separately.
        All campaign 1970 negatives are held by B&G International.
        Pat Evans, Photo Editor, Campaign 1970
        - 1970 April
          - 1970 April 6 (Box 99)
          - 1970 April 7 (Box 99)
          - 1970 April 8 (Box 99)
          - Dedication of Onondaga Community College, 1970 April 21 (Box 99)
          - TV interview - NY City, 1970 April 21 (Box 99)
          - Bill signing: Environmental Bill (Earth Day), 1970 April 22 (Box 99)
          - Earth Day Program - NY City, 1970 April 22 (Box 99)
          - Labor Press Conference, 1970 April 23 (Box 99)
          - Rockland County Republican Committee Breakfast, 1970 April 24 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing: Thruway Exit Bill, 1970 April 24 (Box 99)
          - Erie County Republican Committee Dinner - Buffalo, 1970 April 27 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing: Buffalo, 1970 April 27 (Box 99)
          - SUNY/Alfred - Dedication of Residence Hall and Library, 1970 April 27 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 April 28 (Box 99)
            - Rubella Bill, 1970 April 28 (Box 99)
            - Residential Accommodations Bill for Mentally Retarded, 1970 April 28 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
            - UFT Retirement Bill, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
            - Labor Leaders Bill, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
            - Consumer Package Bill, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
            - Public Service Commission Bill, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
          - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1970 April 29 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing, 1970 April 30 (Box 99)
            - Labor Bill, 1970 April 30 (Box 99)
            - Graduating Class of Modem School (Black Children), 1970 April 30 (Box 99)
            - Association for Help of Retarded Children, 1970 April 30 (Box 99)
        - 1970 May
          - National Weather Services Medal - 100th Anniversary, 1970 May 1 (Box 99)
          - Conference on the Aging, 1970 May 1 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 May 1 (Box 99)
          - New York Police Department St. George Society Breakfast - Waldorf (Bob Hope Attended), 1970 May 3 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing, 1970 May 5 (Box 99)
            - Snowmobile, 1970 May 5 (Box 99)
            - Drug Abuse Conference - Albany (400 Religious Leaders), 1970 May 5 (Box 99)
            - Tea for Mary Lord - Executive Mansion, 1970 May 5 (Box 99)
            - Greater New York Hospital Association Dinner, 1970 May 5 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 May 6 (Box 99)
            - Modernization of Pen Central, Hudson/Harlem Division, 1970 May 6 (Box 99)
          - Westchester Womens Republican Club - Eastchester, 1970 May 7 (Box 99)
          - New York Urban League Dinner, 1970 May 7 (Box 99)
          - Antidefamation League Breakfast - B'nai B'rith, 1970 May 10 (Box 99)
          - Salute to Israel Parade - NY City, 1970 May 10 (Box 99)
          - Yiddish Writers Union - Statler Hilton, 1970 May 10 (Box 99)
          - Real Estate board Breakfast - Bronx, 1970 May 12 (Box 99)
          - Bronx Promenade Apartments Groundbreaking, 1970 May 12 (Box 99)
          - Catholic Interracial council Dinner - Hilton (Harry Van Arsdale Attended), 1970 May 12 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 May 13 (Box 99)
            - Narcotic Issue - Washington DC, 1970 May 13 (Box 99)
            - Swearing In - Parole Board, 1970 May 13 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Kittay House - Jewish Home for the Aged - Bronx, 1970 May 14 (Box 99)
          - NYS. Council on Arts - 5th Annual Awards, 1970 May 14 (Box 99)
          - Niagara Frontier Groundbreaking - Performing Arts, 1970 May 14 (Box 99)
          - Livingston County Republican Dinner - Geneseo, 1970 May 15 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing, 1970 May 15 (Box 99)
            - Heart Bill, 1970 May 15 (Box 99)
          - Ithaca College commencement, 1970 May 16 (Box 99)
          - Help for Retarded Children Dinner - Americana, 1970 May 16 (Box 99)
          - National Academy of TV Arts & Sciences, 1970 May 18 (Box 99)
          - Senator Wagner Memorial Dinner for Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - Pierre Hotel, 1970 May 18 (Box 99)
          - American Insurance Association 1970 Annual Meeting, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signings, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
            - NYS. Fire Fighters Association Bill, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
            - Optometry, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
            - Police Pension Bill, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
            - Bridge & Tunnel Bill, 1970 May 19 (Box 99)
          - Governor Attends 25th Anniversary of Opening of U.N. Session, 1970 May 20 (Box 99)
          - Labor Leaders At Massena, 1970 May 20 (Box 99)
          - Governor with Senator Flynn & Police Board, 1970 May 20 (Box 99)
          - Bill Signing, 1970 May 20 (Box 99)
            - Wild Species Bill, 1970 May 20 (Box 99)
          - Dedication of Watertown Office Building, 1970 May 21 (Box 99)
          - Dedication of Hudson Highlands Park, 1970 May 23 (Box 99)
          - New York State University Construction Fund, 1970 May 25 (Box 99)
          - A.M.A. conference on Pollution, 1970 May 25 (Box 99)
          - NY State Police Academy Dinner - Albany, 1970 May 26 (Box 99)
          - NY State Association of Community Mental Health Board Meeting - Albany, 1970 May 26 (Box 99)
          - Dedication of New York Power Pool Center, 1970 May 26 (Box 99)
          - Montgomery County Republican Committee Dinner - Amsterdam, 1970 May 26 (Box 99)
          - Employ the Handicapped Luncheon - Plaza, 1970 May 27 (Box 99)
          - Mt. Sinai Dinner - Gus Levy, 1970 May 27 (Box 99)
          - Ribbon Cutting: Cross Bay Parkway Bridge, 1970 May 28 (Box 99)
          - Nassau County Republican Committee Dinner - Garden City, 1970 May 28 (Box 99)
          - Caribbean American Dinner Dance, 1970 May 29 (Box 99)
        - 1970 June
          - Labor Leaders Reception, 1970 June 1 (Box 99)
          - Governor & Nassau County Campaign Leader, 1970 June 2 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Robert Moses Plaza, 1970 June 2 (Box 99)
          - American Association of Museums, 1970 June 3 (Box 99)
          - Conference of Mayors & Officers, 1970 June 3 (Box 99)
          - Republican State Committee Luncheon & Dinner (Roosevelt & Waldorf), 1970 June 4 (Box 99)
          - Tarrytown Centennial, 1970 June 6 (Box 99)
          - Puerto Rican Day Parade - NY City, 1970 June 7 (Box 99)
          - Buffalo Ground Breaking - Urban Development Corporation, 1970 June 8 (Box 99)
          - Licensed Practical Nurses Association - NY City, 1970 June 8 (Box 99)
          - Annual Health Conference, 1970 June 8 (Box 99)
          - Division of Housing & Community Workshop - Hilton, 1970 June 9 (Box 99)
          - Washington DC- Republican Candidates Conference Luncheon, 1970 June 10 (Box 99)
          - Republican Committee Spring Cocktail Party - Farmingdale, 1970 June 10 (Box 99)
          - Padua Street Festival - NY City, 1970 June 11 (Box 99)
          - Endorsement: Longshoremen, 1970 June 11 (Box 99)
          - SUNY/Farmingdale - Agricultural & Technical College, 51st Annual Commencement, 1970 June 12 (Box 99)
          - National Federation of Jewish Men's Clubs - Grossingers, 1970 June 14 (Box 99)
          - 1970 June 15 (Box 99)
          - 1970 June 16 (Box 99)
          - Uniformed Fire Fighters Association Endorsement, 1970 June 18 (Box 99)
          - Institute of Rapid Transit Luncheon w/William Ronan (Waldorf), 1970 June 18 (Box 99)
          - Reception for Cardinal Cooke - Guild of Catholic Lawyers Cocktail Reception At Columbus Club - NY City, 1970 June 18 (Box 99)
          - Child Guidance Center Dinner Dance in Flushing Meadows Park, 1970 June 18 (Box 99)
          - Swearing In: Robert E. Fischer as Deputy Attorney General - Gotham Hotel, 1970 June 18 (Box 99)
          - Endorsement: Leather Goods, Plastics, etc., 1970 June 19 (Box 99)
          - Ahapa Banquet - Grossingers, 1970 June 19 (Box 99)
          - Endorsement: Painters, 1970 June 20 (Box 99)
          - S. Frank Raferty Testimonial Dinner - Americana, 1970 June 20 (Box 99)
          - Nassau County Help for Retarded, 1970 June 20 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Lubavicher Yeshivoth - Brooklyn, 1970 June 21 (Box 99)
          - NYS. Summer Institute on Alcohol Problems - Buffalo Campus, 1970 June 22 (Box 99)
          - Urban Development Agreement Regarding Ten Eyck and New Bus Terminal-Albany, 1970 June 22 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Plaque honoring John D. Rockefeller 3rd at Philharmonic Hall - Lincoln Center, 1970 June 23 (Box 99)
          - Mid-Atlantic Governors Conference - Annapolis, MD, 1970 June 24 (Box 99)
          - Swearing In: Henry Diamond - Commissioner of Environmental Conservation, 1970 June 25 (Box 99)
          - Endorsement: Policemen's Benevolent Association Hotel New Yorker, 1970 June 25 (Box 99)
          - United Jewish Appeal - Person-to-Person Meeting, 1970 June 25 (Box 99)
          - Inspection of Development Sites in New York Area, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Mottage Site - Bronx, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Inwood North - New York, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Inwood South - New York, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Twin Pines Village - Brooklyn, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Castleton Park - Staten Island, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Pier Housing Site - Staten Island, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
            - Co-op City Flying Tour - Bronx, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
          - Borough Hall - President Connor's Reception, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
          - Floyd Bennett Field - Officers Club Luncheon, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
          - Hydrofoil Ride - Battery Park, 1970 June 26 (Box 99)
          - Perry P. Duryea, Jr.- Testimonial Ball, 1970 June 27 (Box 99)
          - Washington County Republican Committee Koffee Klatch, 1970 June 29 (Box 99)
          - Hamilton County Republican Committee Reception - Glens Falls, 1970 June 29 (Box 99)
          - Warren County Republican Committee Reception - Spectacular, 1970 June 29 (Box 99)
          - NY Society of Newspaper Editors Luncheon - Saratoga Springs, 1970 June 29 (Box 99)
          - NY Conference of Bricklayers Endorsement, 1970 June 30 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Lake George Institute of History, Art & Science, 1970 June 30 (Box 99)
        - 1970 July
          - Fund Transfer: From Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Authority to M.T.A., 1970 July 1 (Box 99)
          - Holidays, 1970 July 2-15
          - Co-op City Taping of TV Special, 1970 July 16 (Box 99)
          - Jones Beach Walking Tour, 1970 July 18 (Box 99)
          - Arts & Entertainment Committee Formation, 1970 July 20 (Box 99)
          - Governor with Assemblymen H. Clark Bell & Ben Gillman, 1970 July 23 (Box 99)
          - Swearing In: Dr. Sal J. Prezioso, as Commissioner of Parks & Recreation, 1970 July 24 (Box 99)
          - Candidates Breakfast - Waldorf, 1970 July 27 (Box 99)
          - Bank Opening: Banco Popular Ribbon Cutting -Garment Center (Puerto Ricans), 1970 July 27 (Box 99)
          - Governor Rides Penn Central from Pleasantville to New York, 1970 July 28 (Box 99)
          - Judge Rosenman Endorses Governor, 1970 July 28 (Box 99)
          - Rotterdam Shoporama, 1970 July 29 (Box 99)
          - Allied Printing Trade Council of New York Convention - Albany, 1970 July 29 (Box 99)
          - Photo Session: Upstate Candidates - Thruway House, 1970 July 29 (Box 99)
          - NYS. Association of Chiefs of Police Dinner - Albany, 1970 July 29 (Box 99)
          - Drug Abuse Meetings: shaker Junior High School - Latham, NY, 1970 July 30 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Douglas D. Couser Orange County Infirmary, 1970 July 30 (Box 99)
          - Orange County Fair: Government, Labor & Industry Day - Middletown, 1970 July 30 (Box 99)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Valhalla, 1970 July 31 (Box 99)
          - Governor Photographed w/Lt. Governor, 1970 July 31 (Box 99)
          - Press Conference - Pocantico Hills, 1970 July 31 (Box 99)
        - 1970 August
          - Bayveiw Narcotics Rehabilitation Center - 550 West 20th Street - NY City, 1970 August 3 (Box 99)
          - Edgecombe Rehabilitation Center - 611 Edgecombe Avenue, 1970 August 3 (Box 99)
          - Addicts Rehabilitation Center-253 West 123rd Street, 1970 August 3 (Box 99)
          - Pesticides Hearings: New York Academy of Medicine, sponsored by NYS. Environmental Comm, 1970 August 3 (Box 99)
          - Conference on Drug Abuse: Queens, 1970 August 4 (Box 99)
          - Dedication: Cornerstone of Center for Retarded - Williamsburg section of Brooklyn, 1970 August 4 (Box 99)
          - Spanish TV Interview, 1970 August 5 (Box 99)
          - Federal Rehabilitation Medallion - Photos of blind man & crippled representing group, 1970 August 5 (Box 99)
          - Co-Operative Housing Tenants (Harold Brown, etc.) receive check from Governor, 1970 August 5 (Box 99)
          - John Lomenzo, Secretary of State, at 55th Street, 1970 August 5 (Box 99)
          - NYS. Construction & Trades Council Convention at Rochester - Peter Brennan, 1970 August 6 (Box 100)
          - International Typographical Union Convention - Buffalo, 1970 August 6 (Box 100)
          - Saratoga - Private Party (Eugene Ormandy), 1970 August 7 (Box 100)
          - Baseball Game: "Rocky's Team" vs. Cast of "1776" - Central Park (photos by Murray Mondschein), 1970 August 8 (Box 100)
          - Appointment: Betty Furness as Chairman of State Consumer Protection Board, 1970 August 10 (Box 100)
          - National Governors Conference - Lake of Ozarks, Missouri (photos show Governor with his brother, Winthrop Rockefeller), 1970 August 11 (Box 100)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Sweet Home Junior High School - Amherst, NY, 1970 August 12 (Box 100)
          - Warsaw Village Picnic (Wyoming County Highway Superintendents Picnic), 1970 August 12 (Box 100)
          - Webster Beach Park Annual Republican Picnic, 1970 August 12 (Box 100)
          - Monroe County Park Bans Concert Drop-In - Rochester, 1970 August 12 (Box 100)
          - Puerto Rican Week Celebration, 1970 August 12 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Environmental Air Monitoring Station, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Monroe County College Environmental Forum, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - WHEC/TV Interview on Environment (Rochester channel 10), 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Geneva Farm Leaders Luncheon - NYS. Agricultural Experimental Station, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Propane Car (anti-pollution) designed by Buffalo Students, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Grape Picking Machine - Don Wickham, Comm. of Agriculture & Marketing-Hector, NY, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Women's Suffrage Group at Eisenhower College - Seneca Falls (Wilma Rogalin), 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Ox Roast - Schuyler Count Republican Committee Event, 1970 August 13 (Box 100)
          - Associates for Rockefeller - Breakfast at Overseas Press Club, 1970 August 14 (Box 100)
          - Governor & Lt. Governor in Shirt Sleeves (special photo for poster), 1970 August 14 (Box 100)
          - March on Drugs (Drug-Out) Parade - NY City, 1970 August 14 (Box 100)
          - Governor meets with students from various colleges - 55th Street Office, 1970 August 14 (Box 100)
          - Jacob Riis Park Beach Walking Tour, 1970 August 15 (Box 100)
          - Jewish Leaders meet with Governor at 55th Street, 1970 August 17 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: Queens Children's Hospital for Mentally Retarded - Bellrose, 1970 August 18 (Box 100)
          - Storefront Opening: Forest Hills 106-21 Continental Avenue, 1970 August 18 (Box 100)
          - Storefront Opening: Bronx - 315 East Fordham Road, 1970 August 18 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Fireman's Association Convention - Watertown, 1970 August 19 (Box 100)
          - Jefferson Community College Meeting with Students - Watertown, 1970 August 19 (Box 100)
          - Onondaga County Environmental Forum - Syracuse, 1970 August 19 (Box 100)
          - Teamsters Joint Council 16.-.Reception & Annual Convention Dinner -.Kiamesha, 1970 August 19 (Box 100)
          - Federation of Women's Republican Club of New York State Dinner, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Headquarters Opening: Independents for Rockefeller - Binghamton, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Combined Service Club Luncheon - Waverly, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Tioga County Fair - Owego, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Chemung Sewage Plant (#1) Inspection - Elmira, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Chemung County Environmental Forum - Elmira, 1970 August 20 (Box 100)
          - Richard Rodgers is made Honorary Chairman of Arts & Entertainment Committee, 1970 August 24 (Box 100)
          - Franklin County Fair - Malone, 1970 August 25 (Box 100)
          - 159th Anniversary of Purchase of Fort Ticonderoga & Garrison Grounds (Pell Reception), 1970 August 25 (Box 100)
          - Oneida county Airport Reception, 1970 August 25 (Box 100)
          - Combined Service Club Luncheon - Malone, 1970 August 25 (Box 100)
          - WKTV (Utica) Taping, 1970 August 25 (Box 100)
          - Women's Lib March in NY City (pix by Howard Legge), 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - Baseball Game: "Rocky's Team" vs. cast of "Shakespeare in the Park" (Mondschein), 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Oriskany, 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - Combined Service Club - Cortland, 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - NYS. veterans Home Visit (Home for the Aged) - Oxford, 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - Chenango County Republican Womens Club - Annual Family Picnic - Norwich, 1970 August 26 (Box 100)
          - New York State Salutes Miss Universe - Marisol Malaret of Puerto Rico, 1970 August 27 (Box 100)
        - 1970 September
          - Private Breakfast with Clergy - Hilton, 1970 September 2 (Box 100)
          - Transit PBA - Meeting at Royal Manhattan, 1970 September 2 (Box 100)
          - Syracuse Annual Farm Dinner, 1970 September 2 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Fair Exhibitors Breakfast - Syracuse Fairgrounds, 1970 September 3 (Box 100)
          - Governor Plants State Sugar Maple - Fairgrounds, 1970 September 3 (Box 100)
          - NYS. AFL7CIO 13th Constitutional Convention - Kiamesha, 1970 September 3 (Box 100)
          - 73rd Annual National Zionist Convention - Waldorf, 1970 September 3 (Box 100)
          - Columbia County Fair - Chatham, 1970 September 5 (Box 100)
          - Catskill Hotel Tours, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
            - Pioneer Country Club/ Breakfast, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
            - Raleigh Hotel - Kiamesha, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
            - Concord Hotel - Kiamesha, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
            - Pines Hotel - South Fallsburg, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
            - Browns Hotel - Loch Sheldrake, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
          - Jewish Teachers Association Reception - Grossingers, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)